Guide to the James Harvey Rogers Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Index to Selected Correspondents
  - Morgenthau, Henry (1891-1963)
    - 10 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1934 October 9 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 19 (Box 15)
      - 1935 February 4 (Box 16)
      - 1935 February 21 (Box 16)
      - 1936 September 29 (Box 19)
      - 1938 September 27 (Box 23)
    - 18 TL (copies, drafts) and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 November 3 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 2 (Box 13)
      - 1934 April 21 (Box 14)
      - 1934 September 29 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 2 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 5 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 17 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 18 (Box 15)
      - 1934 October 27 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 9 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 10 (Box 15)
      - 1934 November 23 (Box 15)
      - 1934 undated (2) (Box 15)
      - 1935 February 2 (Box 16)
      - 1935 February 4 (Box 16)
      - 1935 May 18 (Box 16)
      - 1938 September 26 (Box 23)
    - TL (copy) written by George Frederick Warren (1874-1938), Washington, D.C., 1934 February 7 (Box 13)
  - Murphy, Louis T. (1876-1936)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Dubuque, Iowa, 1933 January 18 (Box 11)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1933 February 4 (Box 11)
  - Mussolini, Benito (1883-1945). TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1935 May 28 (Box 16)
  - Nelson, William Lester (1875-1946)
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1930 May 7 (Box 16)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, New Haven, 1930 May 27 (Box 7)
  - Noble, S. Randolph (1887-)
    - 8 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Montreal
      - 1931 June 27 (Box 8)
      - 1931 September 25 (Box 9)
      - 1932 February 20 (Box 10)
      - 1934 October 14 (Box 15)
      - 1935 December 27 (Box 16)
      - 1936 November 20 (Box 19)
      - 1936 December 8 (Box 20)
      - 1936 December 29 (Box 20)
    - 2 TLS to Robert Sargent Shriver, Montreal
      - 1937 April 21 (Box 20)
      - 1938 October 18 (Box 23)
  - Oliphant, Herman (1884-1939)
    - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1930 May 20 (Box 7)
      - 1933 November 15 (Box 13)
      - 1934 September 14 (Box 15)
      - 1935 July 29 (Box 17)
      - 1936 September 26 (Box 19)
    - 4 TL (copies) and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, various places
      - 1933 November 16 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 2 (Box 13)
      - 1934 February 16 (Box 13)
      - 1934 March 23 (Box 14)
    - TL (copy) written by George Frederick Warren (1874-1938), 1934 Feb 1, Washington, D.C. (Box 14)
  - Owen, Robert Latham (1856-1947).
    - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 January 8 (Box 20)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1933 August 19 (Box 12)
  - Pareto, Vilfredo Frederico Damaso (1848-1923)
    - 12 ALS to James Harvey Rogers, Celigny, Switzerland
      - 1915 October 22 (Box 1)
      - 1915 December 14 (Box 1)
      - 1916 February 9 (Box 1)
      - 1916 April 7 (Box 1)
      - 1916 December 12 (Box 1)
      - 1917 March 28 (Box 1)
      - 1917 March 30 (Box 1)
      - 1919 October 28 (Box 1)
      - 1920 January 10 (Box 1)
      - 1920 February 11 (Box 1)
      - 1921 August 17 (Box 1)
      - 1921 December 31 (Box 1)
    - ALS to Edwin Bidwell Wilson, Celigny, Switzerland, 1908 September 16 (Box 1)
  - Pearson, Frank Ashmore (1887-)
    - TL (copy) written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1939 August 26 (Box 24)
  - Peltason, Paul Evans (1898-)
    - 2 TL (copy) and telegram written by James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
      - 1933 August 1 (Box 12)
      - 1933 October 18 (Box 12)
  - Rogers, James Harvey (1886-1939)
    - Acheson, Dean Gooderham (1893-)
      - TLS to James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1937 January 11 (Box 20)
    - Adelman, Adrien
      - 8 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1938 March 1 (Box 22)
        - 1938 March 10 (Box 22)
        - 1938 March 29 (Box 22)
        - 1938 November 4 (Box 23)
        - 1938 November 29 (Box 23)
        - 1938 December 7 (Box 23)
        - 1938 December 13 (Box 23)
        - 1939 January 25 (Box 23)
    - Angell, James Rowland (1869-1949)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, no place
        - 1935 April 18 (Box 16)
        - 1935 November 7 (Box 17)
    - Angell, James Waterhouse (1898-)
      - 2 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1928 May 8 (Box 5)
        - 1928 May 15 (Box 5)
    - Bakewell, Charles Montague (1867-1957). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1933 March 2 (Box 11)
    - Balogh, Thomas (1905-)
      - 13 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1933 September 11 (Box 12)
        - 1934 [Jan] undated (Box 13)
        - 1934 February 21 (Box 13)
        - 1935 April 26 (Box 16)
        - 1936 August 11 (Box 19)
        - 1936 September 14 (Box 19)
        - 1936 October 13 (Box 19)
        - 1936 November 2 (Box 19)
        - 1936 November 26 (Box 19)
        - 1936 December 2 (Box 19)
        - 1936 December 4 (Box 20)
        - 1936 December 10 (Box 20)
        - 1937 January undated (Box 20)
    - Belser, Irvine F. 26 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1933 July 12-1938 December 27 (Box 12–23)
    - Berle, Adolph August (1895-)
      - 13 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1933 February 7 (Box 11)
        - 1936 February 18 (Box 18)
        - 1936 February 26 (Box 18)
        - 1936 March 13 (Box 18)
        - 1936 April 24 (Box 18)
        - 1936 December 11 (Box 20)
        - 1937 January 14 (Box 20)
        - 1937 March 4 (Box 20)
        - 1937 October 21 (Box 21)
        - 1938 March 25 (Box 22)
        - 1938 October 28 (Box 23)
        - 1939 March 7 (Box 24)
        - 1939 April 17 (Box 24)
    - Barnays, Edwin L. (1891-). 36 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1931 November 9-1938 December 5 (Box 9–23)
    - Bongiorno, Andrew (1900-). 47 ALS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1922-1935 (Box 1–17)
    - Boyd, George Adams (1898-). 20 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1921-1938 (Box 1–23)
    - Bratter, Herbert Max (1900-)
      - 20 ALS, TLS and memos to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1934 April 10 (Box 14)
        - 1934 April 11 (Box 14)
        - 1934 April 17 (Box 14)
        - 1934 April 18 (Box 14)
        - 1934 April 28 (Box 14)
        - 1934 April 29 (Box 14)
        - 1934 May 3 (Box 14)
        - 1934 May 16 (Box 14)
        - 1934 May 17 (Box 14)
        - 1934 May 24 (Box 14)
        - 1934 May 25 (2) (Box 14)
        - 1934 July 17 (Box 15)
        - 1934 September 25 (Box 15)
        - 1934 September 27 (Box 15)
        - 1934 October 11 (Box 15)
        - 1934 November 14 (Box 15)
        - 1936 February 10 (Box 18)
        - 1936 February 20 (Box 18)
        - 1936 February 28 (Box 18)
        - 1936 October 20 (Box 19)
    - Brown, Harry Gunnison (1880-). 26 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1923 February 16-1939 May 2 (Box 1–24)
    - Bulkley, Robert Johns (1880-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1938 May 9 (Box 22)
    - Burtness, Ogler Burton (1884-)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1923 December 19 (Box 2)
        - 1931 April 1 (Box 8)
    - Bush, Prescott Sheldon (1895-). 2 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1938 February 8 (2) (Box 22)
    - Butler, Nicholas Murray (1862-1947)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1932 February 9 (Box 10)
        - 1932 December 28 (Box 11)
    - Chandler, Lester Vernon (1905-)
      - 6 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1931 March 24 (Box 8)
        - 1931 July 17 (Box 8)
        - 1932 December 20 (Box 11)
        - 1933 August 2 (Box 12)
        - 1933 November 16 (Box 12)
        - 1934 March 17 (Box 12)
    - Chiang, Mei-ling (Soong) (1897-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Kuling, Kiangsi, China, 1934 July 23 (Box 15)
    - Clark, Evans (1888-)
      - 9 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1932 March 25 (Box 10)
        - 1932 March 31 (Box 10)
        - 1932 June 16 (Box 10)
        - 1932 August 8 (Box 11)
        - 1932 August 12 (Box 11)
        - 1932 August 17 (Box 11)
        - 1933 February 21 (Box 11)
        - 1935 February 20 (Box 16)
        - 1935 April 5 (Box 16)
    - Cohrssen, Hans Robert Ludwig (1905-). 40 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1936-1939 (Box 17–24)
    - Coker, David Robert (1870-1938)
      - 11 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1922 April 17 (Box 1)
        - 1926 May 22 (Box 3)
        - 1928 January 26 (Box 4)
        - 1931 October 17 (Box 9)
        - 1932 January 11 (Box 9)
        - 1932 January 16 (Box 9)
        - 1932 January 20 (Box 9)
        - 1932 January 22 (Box 9)
        - 1932 July 23 (Box 11)
        - 1932 December 28 (Box 11)
        - 1936 March 18 (Box 18)
    - Coker, Francis Williams (1878-1963)
      - 2 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
        - 1930 February 4 (Box 7)
        - 1935 June 12 (Box 16)
    - Commons, John Rogers (1862-1945)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1928 April 17 (Box 5)
        - 1928 April 21 (Box 5)
    - Copland, Douglas Berry (1894-)
      - 10 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1934 January 5 (Box 13)
        - 1936 September 29 (Box 19)
        - 1936 October 5 (Box 19)
        - 1936 October 20 (Box 19)
        - 1937 August 19 (Box 21)
        - 1938 January 5 (Box 22)
        - 1938 January 12 (Box 22)
        - 1938 January undated (Box 22)
        - 1938 April 27 (Box 22)
        - 1938 December 22 (Box 23)
    - Copeland, Morris Albert (1895-)
      - 5 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1926 May 20 (Box 3)
        - 1927 May 31 (Box 4)
        - 1928 April 14 (Box 5)
        - 1928 May 3 (Box 5)
        - 1932 December 2 (Box 11)
    - Cowles, Alfred (1891-)
      - 15 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Colorado Springs, Col.
        - 1932 May 2 (Box 10)
        - 1932 September 30 (Box 11)
        - 1936 March 26 (Box 18)
        - 1936 June 2 (Box 18)
        - 1936 November 25 (2) (Box 19)
        - 1937 May 5 (Box 21)
        - 1937 July 26 (Box 21)
        - 1937 September 20 (Box 21)
        - 1937 October 1 (Box 21)
        - 1937 October 22 (Box 21)
        - 1938 October 1 (Box 23)
        - 1939 March 1 (Box 24)
        - 1939 March 25 (Box 24)
        - 1939 April 5 (Box 24)
    - Cross, Oliver Harlan (1870-)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1931 October 26 (Box 9)
        - 1932 July 6 (Box 10)
        - 1935 November 5 (Box 17)
    - Cross, Wilbur Lucius (1862-1948)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
        - 1922 December 30 (Box 2)
        - 1935 November 7 (Box 17)
    - Resumé and obituaries, 1935 February 27 (Box 16)
    - Davenport, Herbert Joseph (1861-1931)
      - 3 TL and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
        - 1925 undated (Box 3)
        - 1928 March 2 (Box 5)
        - 1928 March 9 (Box 5)
    - Dewey, John (1859-1952). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1931 December 15 (Box 9)
    - Downey, Sheridan (1884-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, no place, 1939 February 23 (Box 24)
    - Dunn, James Clement (1890-)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1935 December 5 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 12 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 30 (Box 17)
    - Early, Stephen Tyree (1889-1951)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1933 December 14 (Box 13)
        - 1938 September 27 (Box 23)
    - Eccles, Marriner Stoddard (1890-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 December 6 (Box 21)
    - Edie, Lionel Danforth (1893-). 29 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1929-1939 (Box 6–24)
    - Edmiston, Henry H.
      - 6 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1930 February 27 (Box 7)
        - 1933 August 22 (Box 12)
        - 1936 January 16 (Box 17)
        - 1936 August 20 (Box 19)
        - 1937 August 1 (Box 21)
        - 1939 January 16 (Box 23)
    - Ely, Richard Theodore (1854-1943)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1933 February 14 (Box 11)
        - 1933 April 4 (Box 11)
    - Farrand, Livingston (1867-1939)
      - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
        - 1923 March 7 (Box 2)
        - 1923 March 24 (Box 2)
        - 1923 June 11 (Box 2)
        - 1925 October 5 (Box 3)
    - Feis, Herbert (1893-). 35 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1933-1939 (Box 11–24)
    - Fish, Hamilton (1888-). Telegram to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1932 October 24 (Box 11)
    - Fisher, Irving (1867-1947)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New Haven
        - 1930 March 3 (Box 7)
        - 1937 October 24 (Box 21)
        - 1938 May 27 (Box 22)
    - Foster, William Trufant (1879-1950)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, no place
        - 1924 March 7 (Box 2)
        - 1924 September 3 (Box 2)
    - Frank, Jerome (1889-1957). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1932 December 9 (Box 11)
    - Fraser, Leon (1889-1945)
      - 3 TLS and TL (copy) to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1936 February 7 (Box 18)
        - 1937 July 29 (Box 21)
        - 1938 January 4 (Box 22)
    - Friedrich, Carl Joachim (1901-). 60 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1923 June 23-1936 April 1 (Box 1–18)
    - Frisch, Ragnar Anton Kittil (1895-)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1930 April 19 (Box 7)
        - 1932 August 20 (Box 11)
        - 1935 October 2 (Box 17)
    - Fry, Charles Luther (1894-). 37 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1924-1937 (Box 2–21)
    - Furniss, Edgar Stephenson (1890-). 104 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1921 February 22-1939 May 30 (Box 1–24)
    - Gallup, George Horace (1901-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1938 December 22 (Box 23)
    - Gay, Edwin Francis (1867-1946). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Cambridge, Mass., 1929 March 22 (Box 6)
    - Gayer, Arthur David (1903-1951). 39 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1933 January 30-1938 August 19 (Box 11–22)
    - Givens, Meredith Bruner (1899-)
      - 16 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1931 November 5 (Box 9)
        - 1931 December 4 (Box 9)
        - 1931 December 23 (Box 9)
        - 1932 February 3 (Box 10)
        - 1932 February 17 (Box 10)
        - 1932 February 20 (Box 10)
        - 1932 February 25 (Box 10)
        - 1932 March 17 (Box 10)
        - 1932 March 30 (Box 10)
        - 1932 May 2 (Box 10)
        - 1932 May 9 (Box 10)
        - 1932 June 10 (Box 10)
        - 1932 June 21 (Box 10)
        - 1932 October 25 (Box 11)
        - 1932 November 4 (Box 11)
        - 1932 December 27 (Box 11)
    - Glass, Carter (1858-1946). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1935 May 27 (Box 16)
    - Goldenweiser, Emanuel Alexander (1883-1953)
      - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1927 January 5 (Box 4)
        - 1927 April 14 (Box 4)
        - 1935 October 24 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 2 (Box 17)
    - Goldsborough, Thomas Alan (1877-1951)
      - 3 telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1932 March 15 (Box 10)
        - 1932 March 22 (2) (Box 10)
    - Gore, Thomas Pryor (1870-1949). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1935 July 20 (Box 17)
    - Green, William (1873-)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1931 December 29 (Box 9)
        - 1932 January 4 (Box 9)
        - 1933 May 10 (Box 12)
    - Haig, Robert Murray (1887-1953)
      - 20 TLS, TL (copies) and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1926 October 9 (Box 3)
        - 1926 October 21 (Box 3)
        - 1926 October 23 (Box 3)
        - 1926 November 29 (Box 3)
        - 1926 December 10 (Box 3)
        - 1926 December 16 (Box 3)
        - 1926 December 17 (Box 3)
        - 1927 January 6 (Box 4)
        - 1927 June 2 (Box 4)
        - 1927 June 7 (Box 4)
        - 1927 June 24 (Box 4)
        - 1927 August 25 (Box 4)
        - 1927 September 1 (Box 4)
        - 1927 October 18 (Box 4)
        - 1927 October 25 (2) (Box 4)
        - 1927 November 18 (Box 4)
        - 1927 December 12 (Box 4)
        - 1930 May 16 (Box 7)
        - 1930 December 22 (Box 8)
    - Hall, Ray Ovid (1891-1953). 57 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1928 May 18-1939 January 11 (Box 5–23)
    - Hansen, Alvin Harvey (1887-)
      - 5 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1934 March 1 (Box 13)
        - 1938 January 3 (Box 22)
        - 1938 January 31 (Box 22)
        - 1938 December 19 (Box 23)
        - 1939 January 13 (Box 23)
    - Hayes, Carlton Joseph Huntley (1882-)
      - 11 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1926 December 14 (Box 3)
        - 1927 January 13 (Box 4)
        - 1927 January 26 (Box 4)
        - 1927 September 20 (Box 4)
        - 1927 November 13 (Box 4)
        - 1927 December 20 (Box 4)
        - 1928 February 2 (Box 4)
        - 1928 February 16 (Box 5)
        - 1928 March 14 (Box 5)
        - 1928 April 16 (Box 5)
        - 1928 May 31 (Box 5)
    - House, Edward Mandell (1858-1938)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1934 October 8 (Box 15)
        - 1934 October 22 (Box 15)
        - 1934 October 25 (Box 15)
    - Hull, Cordell (1871-1939)
      - 4 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1933 November 10 (Box 13)
        - 1935 October 2 (Box 17)
        - 1936 June 17 (Box 19)
        - 1936 August 8 (Box 19)
    - Hunt, Edward Eyre (1885-1953)
      - 33 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1928 January 30 (Box 4)
        - 1928 February 1 (Box 4)
        - 1928 February 14 (Box 5)
        - 1928 February 27 (Box 5)
        - 1928 March 8 (Box 5)
        - 1928 April 4 (Box 5)
        - 1928 April 20 (Box 5)
        - 1928 April 21 (Box 5)
        - 1928 May 24 (Box 5)
        - 1928 June 7 (Box 5)
        - 1928 June 9 (Box 5)
        - 1928 June 14 (Box 5)
        - 1928 June 22 (Box 5)
        - 1928 July 30 (Box 5)
        - 1928 August 13 (Box 5)
        - 1928 August 20 (Box 5)
        - 1928 September 13 (Box 5)
        - 1928 September 27 (Box 5)
        - 1928 September 29 (Box 5)
        - 1928 October 2 (Box 5)
        - 1928 October 3 (Box 5)
        - 1928 October 15 (Box 5)
        - 1929 January 11 (Box 6)
        - 1929 February 6 (Box 6)
        - 1929 February 18 (Box 6)
        - 1929 February 27 (Box 6)
        - 1929 April 27 (Box 6)
        - 1929 November 19 (Box 6)
        - 1929 December 5 (Box 6)
        - 1930 January 3 (Box 6)
        - 1930 February 24 (Box 7)
        - 1930 March 31 (Box 7)
    - Klein, Julius (1886-). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1928 June 16 (Box 6)
    - Knight, Frank Hyneman (1885-)
      - 2 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Chicago
        - 1931 January 20 (Box 8)
        - 1933 April 19 (Box 11)
    - Jackson, Gardner
      - 6 ALS, TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1933 February 25 (Box 11)
        - 1933 May 18 (Box 12)
        - 1933 May 26 (Box 12)
        - 1933 May 31 (Box 12)
        - 1933 June 21 (Box 12)
        - 1933 September 25 (Box 12)
    - Jacobson, Per (1894-1963). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Basle, Switzerland, 1933 November 21 (Box 13)
    - Johnson, Alvin Saunders (1874-). 36 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, New York, 1923-1937 (Box 2–21)
    - Johnson, Nelson Trusler (1887-1954)
      - 6 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1934 July 14 (Box 14)
        - 1934 August 6 (Box 15)
        - 1934 November 28 (Box 15)
        - 1939 February 10 (Box 24)
        - 1939 February 18 (Box 24)
        - 1939 March 7 (Box 24)
    - Jones, Grosvenor Monroe (1883-)
      - 9 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1928 May 3 (Box 5)
        - 1929 January 29 (Box 6)
        - 1929 November 20 (Box 6)
        - 1931 June 19 (2) (Box 8)
        - 1933 September 22 (Box 12)
        - 1933 November 11 (Box 13)
        - 1935 July 30 (Box 17)
        - 1935 October 24 (Box 17)
    - Kemmerer, Edwin Walter (1875-1945)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Princeton, N.J.
        - 1928 October 12 (Box 5)
        - 1928 October 22 (Box 5)
        - 1928 December 4 (Box 5)
    - Kendrick, Myron Slade
      - 11 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Ithaca, N.Y.
        - 1924 October 7 (Box 2)
        - 1925 May 4 (Box 3)
        - 1925 November 10 (Box 3)
        - 1926 October 24 (Box 3)
        - 1927 February 23 (Box 4)
        - 1929 May 12 (Box 6)
        - 1929 May 30 (Box 6)
        - 1930 May 2 (Box 7)
        - 1930 June 2 (Box 7)
        - 1933 May 23 (Box 12)
    - King, Willford Isbell (1880-1962)
      - 4 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1921 June 11 (Box 1)
        - 1922 April 25 (Box 1)
        - 1931 September 23 (Box 9)
        - 1931 November 23 (Box 9)
    - Landis, James McCauley (1899-)
      - 3 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1935 January 25 (Box 16)
        - 1936 January 11 (Box 17)
        - 1936 December 17 (Box 20)
    - Laylin, John Gallup (1902-)
      - 14 ALS and TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1934 April 7 (Box 14)
        - 1934 November 30 (Box 15)
        - 1935 July 24 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 6 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 11 (Box 17)
        - 1935 December 19 (Box 17)
        - 1936 February 11 (Box 18)
        - 1936 July 23 (Box 19)
        - 1936 October 8 (Box 19)
        - 1936 November 12 (Box 19)
        - 1937 January 26 (Box 20)
        - 1937 February 19 (Box 20)
        - 1937 June 21 (Box 21)
        - 1937 August 4 (Box 21)
    - Leavens, Dickson Hammond (1887-). 52 ALS, TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, various places, 1931 November 19-1939 February 6 (Box 9–23)
    - Lee, Ivy Ledbetter (1877-1934)
      - 9 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1931 June 12 (Box 8)
        - 1931 June 23 (Box 8)
        - 1931 July 1 (Box 8)
        - 1931 July 21 (Box 8)
        - 1931 October 6 (Box 9)
        - 1932 March 1 (Box 10)
        - 1932 March 17 (Box 10)
        - 1932 May 26 (Box 10)
        - 1933 December 7 (Box 13)
    - Le Hand, Marguerite A. (1898-1944). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1937 November 9 (Box 21)
    - Lippman, Walter (1889-)
      - TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, New York
        - 1933 December 19 (Box 13)
        - 1934 February 2 (Box 13)
    - Lowden, Frank Orren (1861-1943)
      - 4 TLS to James Harvey Rogers, various places
        - 1931 November 18 (Box 9)
        - 1932 December 22 (Box 11)
        - 1933 January 12 (Box 11)
        - 1933 January 31 (Box 11)
    - McFadden, Louis T. (1876-1936). TLS to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C., 1922 December 29 (Box 2)
    - McIntyre, Marvin Hunter (1878-1943)
      - 10 TLS and telegram to James Harvey Rogers, Washington, D.C.
        - 1934 February 9 (Box 13)
        - 1935 May 28 (Box 16)
        - 1935 October 26 (Box 17)
        - 1935 November 8 (Box 17)
        - 1936 November 17 (Box 19)
        - 1936 December 10 (Box 20)
        - 1937 October 21 (Box 21)
        - 1937 November 3 (Box 21)
        - 1937 November 11 (Box 21)
        - 1939 February 4 (Box 23)
    - MacIver, Robert Morrison (1882-)
      - 9 TLS and telegrams to James Harvey Rogers, New York